Here's where we have, there we go. We're now recording. Yep. Sorry about that. I forgot to hit record.
So Jed, why don't you start over again?
>> Okay. So going back, it is 07:05.
We'll call the meeting to order.
The roll call is
regular members Anne Creme, Scott Bresson, Steve Nelson, and myself present.
There are no other members present, so no alternates will be seated.
The only item on the agenda tonight, no items can be added because this is a special meeting, is
new business discussion
action on Ladano Property on Shawty Mill Road.
And
Eric, if you can let Hank share his screen, we'll
go from there.
>> You got it, Hank. All right, hold on.
I don't know if I lost my when I was trying to
log in here. Here we go.
There we go. Folks see that?
Not yet.
No?
Okay.
Hold on.
>> I'm glad it's a small attendance tonight. This is the most we've struggled with Zoom since we started doing these.
Wow.
Screen sharing has failed.
Oh, man.
Okay.
Let's.
>> Are you doing the share screen at the bottom and the Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I do this all the time. Yeah. Trust me. You got it? Can you see it? No. No. Okay.
>> Let's see.
I'm quite sure why it's I'm getting a message that it's not.
>> You want to close out and have Eric try again? Know I had to do that to get my microphone to work tonight.
Let Let me try this one more time here.
Hello Ian, is that you? There we go.
>> Do you see it? Not yet, but it says it's you started sharing screen. There it is. There we go. Oh my god.
>> Okay. Before you start there, Hank. Yep. Leanne,
are you with us tonight?
>> Yes. I'm sorry. I didn't communicate with you at all about this meeting.
So I apologize.
Don't know if I'm even needed or if you've lined up alternates
>> because I didn't get back to you in time. Well, no alternates are here tonight and I'm happy to have you here, Leanne. So
with
my screen saved, I'm going to call it 707
Leanne joined the meeting and is seated as I'm a regular
>> usually better than this. Yeah, I can see the agenda.
I can't see your screen yet, but
I just started trying.
>> Can other folks see the screen? The PowerPoint? Yeah. Oh, good. Yes.
All right. I don't know what's going on there.
Leanne, did you get into Zoom?
>> Well, I'm still trying. I just I saw the emails from a few minutes ago, and I saw the one from Steve.
So
I went in through the town website and put in the you know, I'm using a landline,
and now I'm trying to call it up on my computer.
>> Okay,
yep. So we're gonna let
Hank
start with his discussion while you're doing that.
We all had problems with Zoom tonight. Something
must be a bad phase of the moon or something.
>> So solar flares.
Solar flare. Yeah, they're doing it.
Okay,
you want me to begin?
Yes, go ahead, Hank. Okay, so I just wanted to just a couple of quick slides to sort of ground everybody again where where we are the location and the value of the the parcel we're talking about. So
folks remember that we have
three open space corridors that are mapped in the town. They were mapped in our 2015
plan of conservation and development.
The lower and they're outlined with the dotted black lines that you see the
Western Highlands Open Space Corridor
is the one there on the lower the southern section, Southwestern section of Andover,
and that includes
the areas that are
currently open space that you see there.
The Hartford Neighborhood Centers area, the the state Bishop Swallow Management Area.
It's the town property there over on the Bolton line there.
And the town property where the transfer station is that connects to the rail trail,
and then you can see the juxtaposition
of the 162
acre Ladano property.
The numbers in parentheses
associated with each parcel are the acreage of them.
So you can see from a larger landscape perspective
from an open space corridor.
The Ladano property is a significant connecting piece it's a large track.
And it's a significant connecting piece among two two blocks of town property the 80 acres that it has the transfer station and connects to the rail trail the Hop River State Park Trail and then the 38 acres of
town land. And if you recall, that was built up with some town land we had, and then the donations that we accepted, I believe last year
from
Tom Talbot and from the Northern Connecticut land trust.
That's that's sort of the the landscape perspective.
This is a map that basically shows some of the natural resources
attributes of the Ladano property.
Dotted
red
lines that you see represent
the ones on the left there
represent the town properties. Wanted to keep showing the juxtaposition of that,
and the square at the bottom is an existing four acre property
owned by Tom Talbot that
in conversations with Tom that he's had with the Conservation Commission. If we were able to acquire the
Ladano parcel, he would be willing to donate that as well so that could actually become part of that that piece there.
The Ladano property is centered around
Monument Hill.
You can see Shotty Mill Road to the north, it butts the Shotty Hill
Shotty Mill Road, I believe it has a little over 1,300 acres of frontage.
You can see the Burnout Brook System,
which immediate you know was adjacent to it, so it has an important sort of watershed juxtaposition
as large forested track helping to belt buffer the high quality of the Burnet Brook system, is a high rated by the DEP as a high water quality. It has wild brown trout and brook trout populations in it. The
dots are the vertical pools. When we did the vertical survey this past spring,
it has a very high concentration of vertical pools.
And to give you an example of that there are 15 vertical pools in this 162
acres.
If you compare that to the over 700 acres of Bishop Swamp,
there are, I believe, nine to 10 vernal pools in that, and the
600 or so acres of
Nathan Hale State Forest, which also only has six to 10 or nine to 10 vernal pools. So it has a very high density of vernal pools.
The other colorations that you see there, the purples and the blues, are other wetlands associated
with the property and wetland soils,
so you see that it has a fair number of wetlands associated with it as well.
The other lines, this is a topographic map underlay that I have, So you can see I think Monument Hill peaks at about six eighty feet somewhere in there, based on the topographic maps. So this gives you an idea of some of the natural resource characters of the property
and the value from a natural resource perspective
of the habitats that it supports both forested as well as wetland. There
are really no trails in there, with the exception of an old carriage road that are Cart Road that runs from Shoddy Mill almost all the way down to
Boston Hill Road right up through the central center of the property it's very walkable through that one path.
There are a couple of side logging trails
that more the kind of dead end, but there is the potential for the establishment of of a recreational trail system through through the property. So that gives you a look at the
the site.
Now if we were to combine
>> what's the what's the big yellow box in the upper right upper left hand corner. That's the town boundary.
So that's the town boundary line there with Bolton.
Okay, thank you. Yep.
>> So
if we combine those contiguous pieces the property
that we already have with the town lands, as well as if we were to acquire the the Ladano piece.
What I don't have in there is the Talbot but that would also be included in that we could have a conservation area that would be about two zero four acres.
You know that would make tentatively
calling this the Monument Hill Conservation Area.
The Red Star would be the area where there would be potential public access. That's along Shoddy Mill Road.
There is a gate that goes that crosses
there that's the where the cart path is. And as you enter that cart on the cart path there's an area that's fairly cleared right now it's in some shrub and herbaceous growth was probably a staging area when they were doing logging operations in there,
which could easily be, you know, fairly dry could easily be converted into a small unimproved parking area
that could support you know that would support the conservation area.
So that's kind of the vision so it showed you the sort of the landscape connectivity
within our open space corridor.
The value of the parcel itself
from its natural resources and potential recreational value,
and then show you how this sort of comes together.
So, any questions about the parcel or its connections before I talk about where we are in the process.
Okay.
So here's where we are. So we undertook an appraisal.
And the appraisal came back
for $486,000
The current asking price is $5.49
500.
We're looking at a potential proposal
of to you know for sale of $500,000
Note
that any purchase would be contingent upon
a successful DEP
grant award
and approval at a town vote. Those are two process pieces that would need to occur.
Have exists in our town open space fund. I think it's a little over $238,000
Connecticut and we're proposing to go to the Connecticut DEP
for their municipal open space grant program,
which funds up to 65%
of the appraised value.
So somebody question.
No. And Eric or Jim please jump in if there's something that you feel needs to be added.
It's important to note that
as of recently we have, we found out that there is a pending private our offer on the parcel.
That's about as much detail as we have on that.
So, it's possible that you know that the
trust and the realtor may accept that the trust may accept that.
We don't know, but we are going forward with the assumption that we're continuing to until we hear that they've, you know, they've actually formally accepted that
we're, we're moving forward as,
as planned to
prepare to submit a proposal because we have a bit of a time crunch. The proposals from the deep are due September
30.
So that's a there and there's a fair number of things that we would need to put together.
And I would be remiss if I didn't thank everybody for taking, you know, taking on quick notice the time out of your busy schedules I'm sure here at the end of summer
to agree to meet tonight. I really appreciate it. Thank you and it's really because we have a time crunch or we wouldn't ask you to do to do that.
What we're seeking tonight is approval for the use of the open space funds for purchase
that would need to be I think a formal recommendation from the Planning and Zoning Commission
to the Board of Selectmen
that
because I believe that's the process that would need to be followed.
So that's kind of where we are.
We need to do
for sort of the next steps would be assuming you approve that and
made a recommendation to the Board of Selectmen
would need to be a special meeting of the Board of Selectmen potentially as early as next week.
We would need several things one from the Board of Selectmen a resolution authorizing the expenditure of the open space funds that's needed
as part of the application.
We also would need approval to sort of enter negotiations
with the real estate agent for the Donnell's trust.
We have mindful
of its short timetable.
Jim and Eric and myself have had conversations with the town attorney, and we do have a prepared draft sales agreement so we've we've got a good sense of that, including some of the contingencies.
And then we would also need from the Board of Selectmen sort of an approval to submit an application to the deep on behalf of the town. And as I mentioned that those applications are due at the
end of the month. I'm about three quarters of the way through peskin:
>> writing of the proposal
which obviously would go through a review process internally.
>> You know so that's a you know that we have a pretty good jump on that as well And I've had several conversations
over the past months and several in the past week
with the program officer for the Department of Environmental Protection,
who runs the municipal support or municipal grant program.
So I know that's a lot but that's kind of you know the gives you a background of the parcel and its importance,
and also gives you a sense of where we are and
sort of the next steps with the Board of Selectmen.
So I'll I'll sort of stop my part presentation there and please Eric or or Jim if there's anything you feel needs to be added chime in.
>> I have a question. Have the owners, the current ownership of the property, have they made any indication that they would like to work with the town to make this a conservation area?
>> Eric, can you answer that? Mean you've had, I think you've probably had the closest conversations
there with
realtors or representatives
of the trust.
I don't see Eric on the screen. Was he off? Is he off and he's muted?
I know they're aware of it and my understanding is when we had a conversation I I've not been a party to any of the conversations.
I do know that there was, you know, the realtor was aware of that.
And then I believe that the
the trust also had indicated that they would not subdivide or they would not move forward
until,
know, because they were aware that we were, you know, we were interested
and that we were potentially moving forward with a
grant proposal.
The realtor did
reconnect with us since there's a new realtor now
to let us know that
the trust
has a you know has received an application and wanted to know where we were in the process. So they're aware of it, and I from based on that I would assume that they're willing to work with us, assuming that
you know, assuming that they didn't have a better deal, right?
Okay, thanks.
>> Hank is the when you talk to the folks at deep,
know is the
says the application is due September 30. Is it a first come first served basis kind of thing and do they have lots of money?
Or is it what's your sense on that?
>> The state has. I know they have a minimum of $5,000,000
slotted for fiscal year 2022
and another 5,000,000 for '23.
May have some additional funding because the states under some pressure because they're behind in the overall open space goals for the state,
which close out in which the goal is through 2023.
I think they're trying to close as much of that gap as they can.
It's very competitive,
Jed.
It's not so much a first come first serve. It's just you know it's a competitive grant application.
There's really no wiggle room on the thirtieth. Have to get it in. It has to be a complete application.
There are
metrics that go out two years. So if we did receive an award, we would have two years to complete their up to two years, depending on the task to complete various things like closure on the property and so forth.
But as far as the application,
we need to get it in on the thirtieth. Would need to be complete and it would be part of a very competitive process.
But
you know, that's that's the nature of these. You know, we don't know because it would depend on the quality of the other other asks going in,
you know how we would fit.
You know, just don't know. Mean, you know the the property does fall within having spent a fair amount of time writing the proposal.
One of the things you have to do is you have to look at a variety of different state initiatives
like the climate change action plan, the State Plan of Conservation Development,
Crocs Regional Plan of Conservation Development,
State Wildlife Action Plan, a number of them a recreational plan,
and the property does align with a number of those fairly well.
Know we've got some, know we certainly have some good stories to tell and good. Think would score highly,
and there are other areas where we don't score as high.
So I think it would really depend. It's competitive grant.
>> Thanks Steve. You want to go now that Eric's
back you want to try your question again? Sure.
>> Problem Eric. We were just interested
since they do have
an offer already on the property.
I was wondering if the owners
had any preference to work with the town in terms of land conservation
or whether they're just going for the highest bidder?
>> I don't know because I've only, I've had a brief conversation with one member of the family,
You know, and
I mean I floated a couple of things. Mean, I said, well, know, if we did, you know, do this, know, we'd be happy to,
you know,
give the family, you know, if we came to some kind of reasonable agreement,
you know we could you know forever designated as the Ladano,
you know.
You know Ladano parcel or Ladano trust or something like that. And she wasn't really that didn't seem to make a hill of beans to her.
My sense was that it's a piece of land, it's an asset to try to unload.
Got it, thank you. I think the question in their minds is going to be,
what was the other offer that did they get?
What is the town willing to offer?
Is it worth their while to try to wait and gamble that they get the higher value?
Or do they go for the offer at hand? And without knowing what the other offer is and what's in their minds,
that's reading tea leaves.
Thank you.
>> Kirk, you know, out of tonight's meeting,
I know we have talked about
you making a motion to approve some stuff and we'll look at that
in a little bit.
Is that all you need at this point to go to the Board of Selectmen next week?
>> Well, think what really
needs to happen is because the Board of Selectmen isn't initiating
this.
This is being initiated by the Conservation Commission
and presumably the Planning and Zoning Commission.
So, it really requires is a request from you
to pursue this
and a statement on your part that you're willing to expend the open space fund,
you know, that this is a priority for the Commission's and you're willing to expend the open space funds
to get it.
>> Okay,
so I'm
copying here and I didn't get too far. How about a statement from me about what
to pursue it?
>> So just
essentially a statement saying
the
board
of or the planning and zoning Commission and the conservation
Commission
think this is a partial the town should attempt to acquire.
And that this represents a really good what you guys think is an appropriate use of the open space funds.
And
that essentially what you're doing is you're looking for
permission
to,
you know, you're looking for for them
to
make an offer
to the Ladanos
you know to purchase this property under the And conditions you
>> when would you need that? I didn't ask when you'd like it.
Two different things.
>> So, am asking the Board of Selectmen to do a special meeting prior to the town meeting,
which is scheduled on, I believe, the eighth. I'll tell you in just a second.
Yeah, by the eighth.
Yeah, on the eighth.
>> So you're thinking they would have a special meeting on the seventh or it would need to be in by then?
Early next Before
the eighth. So like
06:30 on the eighth.
Okay.
>> So
yeah.
Chad, can we just make a motion tonight?
>> We can make a motion tonight. It sounded like Eric was looking for a letter from me to
expound on that motion just a little bit.
I'm sure Hank's got
some stuff that he would do with Board of Selectmen as well from the Conservation Commission.
But it
sounds like Eric's looking for a little bit more than just the fact that we made a motion
here tonight and approved it one way or the other.
And I can do that. If I got a couple of days, I can get that done.
>> Yeah. Eric, would we need a formal letter from the Conservation Commission or
me presenting to the, you know, to the Board of Select on behalf of the, I mean, process
wise?
>> So process wise, I think what should happen is if the Board of Selectmen agrees to a special meeting,
I would say both you and Jed should attend
and you should present
the information you have,
Hank, and
>> then Jed, you should basically
present the motion
that was passed by
the zoning Commission.
And
say we would like to pursue this we'd like to make the motion
I already gave them the town's attorneys draft
of the offer to purchase.
You
know, so they can have reviewed that ahead of time and hopefully if they got any
questions or comments about it ahead of time they can get it back to me so I get it down sturdy
because I mean
ideally the day after that
I would like to,
you know.
Submit it to their.
Yeah,
>> you know When would the 08/24 referral
come here? Or is that not applicable in this case because we're recommended and the Board of Selectmen's not asking?
>> Well, so it will eventually, you will eventually have to have a formal. So, let's talk through long term what needs to happen,
you know, for the town to purchase land.
So, we're going to have to make them an offer. They're going to have to say, yes, we'll consider that. You're going to have to get the grant. Once you got the grant and, you know, an agreement from the state,
then at that point, then what you do is you go back to the Board of Selectmen
or correction, the Board of Selectmen goes to the Planning and Zoning Commission
and specifically
asks
for an 08/24 referral for the purchase of the land.
So, you hold a, not a hearing, but you make a decision as the
planning and zoning commission,
and you send that back to the board of selectmen.
And then the board of selectmen
hold the town meeting,
and a town meeting makes a decision
whether the town should allocate the funds for or not.
Because it's over the point zero five.
Point 5%.
Point 5%,
you know, of the total budget,
not including RAM.
So that
that amount of money automatically
goes to a town meeting for approval.
>> And none of that town meeting stuff can be done at the town meeting scheduled on the eighth because that's just too soon.
>> Correct.
Correct.
Yes.
And you have to officially have an 08/24
referral prior to that anyway.
>> Well, I would assume that the
realtor
is going to tune in to watch the Zoom movie
and so he's going to know what
our plan is.
>> He very well may, yeah. And I mean, I think you're you're maybe
having more sophistication on the part of the realtor
than
is warranted,
but, yeah, a smart realtor might do that.
Yep.
And I'm not saying he's not a smart realtor. I'm just saying that, you know, I'm not sure how many realtors really understand town politics enough to know that that information would be available for him. Yep. Okay.
Any other Commission members have any other
questions?
>> I
have another question. So the $238,000
in town open space fund,
are there any other potential parcels or projects or any other
opportunities
to use that money that the town
would consider? In other words, if we
purchase this property,
is there an opportunity cost
for something else that may be down the road that we need to consider?
>> I mean, there's always other,
know, at least
once a year we look at something and think about the potential, its potential uses and should be considered for open space.
So, is, this would be a pretty big commitment.
You know, now I would also say if we did this,
I would certainly go back to the Board of Finance and say, hey, you know, we need to do what most towns do, which is start funding open space on an annual basis.
Yeah. So, we can build thing back up, but there's also zero guarantee that they're going to say yes, and
that it makes it through the budget process.
So while I think it's a good idea, I think there's a lot of things that are good ideas and not everybody agrees with me.
>> Steve, I can add to that a little bit. I mean, one of the act activities that the Conservation Commission has been undertaking,
and we're we're we're a bit into this, but you know, not having completed it, is we're conducting a natural resource inventory
in preparation for the 2025,
planet conservation development.
And as part of that, we are looking at we're layering various data sets
associated
with parcels
with especially within those open space corridors where you know where we tend to direct
open space acquisitions,
which is obviously if you saw there's three quarters, so there's quite a few parcels. So we've been doing that that mapping process.
We actually have drafted a rubric for
sort of ranking those and trying to trying to get on top of it in a strategic way.
Should parcels become available
so that we can, you know, we can make some decisions.
I mean, you know, it's in order to do this effectively. It's a two part equation.
Eric mentioned one, which is, you know, continual mechanisms to fund
sources of
of purchases
or or purchase a transfer, you know, development rights or conservation easements or acquisitions.
But the other part is being strategic about
where do we really need to do this, and so when they come up,
we're we're not. We're not reacting. We're sort of of this one kind of hit us a little early, but I can tell you that looking at all the data, all the data,
even in our rubric that we have now, the state it's in now in the mapping, the Ladano parcel comes up in the top 10. I mean, it's very it's a it's an important parcel
because of the size and because of all the the the sort of attributes I mentioned
earlier.
But it's it was a good question and one that we're trying to trying to get on top of.
And there are also sources of external funding beyond the DEP grant. There are farmland preservation and various other sources, and I believe that over the next few years there will be a push on that.
Because, you know, the state's trying to achieve some goals. So, there may be even further opportunities.
There's nothing that prevents us if we were to go forward and get a successful award. There's nothing that prevents us from going in for another parcel in 2023.
>> Thanks, Hank and Eric. That's very helpful. I mean, knowing that you guys developed the rubric and this falls into the top 10
and based on the available properties
now,
this seems like it's right at the top of the list, right?
>> Yeah. Yeah, it's a it's a strong. I mean, to give you the an idea, the top two on that list are existing ones.
I mean, in in our scoring room, but they're Bishop Swamp Wildlife Management Area and Nathan Hale State Forest. They obviously would score very high because they're huge, right? They have a lot of habitats and all that sort of thing, so they're the top scores out of that, you know. But then you get into some other parcels in the town that are large,
especially
if you start to combine them, you know, like the post farm area, you know, that that's broken into multiple parcels.
Arguably, that's a you know, that's probably one of the most important parcels in, you know, the the the sequence of those in in the town. And by the way, if you go back to the planet conservation and development from 2015, they call out some of these,
like the post farm. They didn't necessarily call O'Donnell, but they call out larger parcels in some of those. And unfortunately, did call out some that we've already lost opportunities on because
we hadn't we hadn't done an activity like this and we weren't sort of ready for it and they just sort of hit the market. And then you know we end up having a reaction. Sometimes we don't even find out about it until you know that's already sold.
Sure, so we're trying to we're trying to be proactive, which is, you know, it's very difficult with smaller towns where the resources are stretched.
You know, there's it's, you know, it's it's it's very difficult. It's, you know, if you're a large town and you've got large budgets and you've got GIS department and things like that, you know, and
but I also think the state recognizes that, you know, when you know folks like us are coming in for applications,
they recognize that, you know, it's a little little little harder for us to
put all this together.
Sure.
I'm good, thank you.
>> I do think it's important to note, you know, when Hank was talking about the planet conservation development,
I think there were three
things in there from the survey that's coming up on six or seven years old that people were willing to pay more taxes on. And
one of them was the purchase of open space stuff. Now this
isn't going to cost us any tax dollars because it's already money put aside. We're going to have to replenish that pot.
And I think the
nature
that Hank explained
to us on why it's so great stands
on its own, but the fact that if we can get at least half of it paid for
by a grant,
And
who knows how the vote would go, but you sure make a compelling
reason that we ought to take advantage of this one and we have not made any progress
on increasing our open space
properties in the last several years.
This
is
helpful for all that stuff.
Okay, Eric, anything else you wanted to share with us on
this?
>> No, I mean, really my job as the administrator is just trying to facilitate
this.
I mean, see this is coming from the commissions, not from me personally,
but I agree with it.
You know,
that's all I got to say.
>> Okay.
So, Hank, I guess at this point, if you could stop sharing your screen.
Will do.
I
>> know Jim you made up a
draft motion for us to
use as a starting point here.
Do you have that
such that you can display it?
Think I can if you don't have it.
>> I've made some changes to it. I'd be happy to read it.
>> I did read it. I don't know that I've read your changes.
>> No.
I just I put it together very quickly and there was just some
minor changes. And actually, I put forth four recommendations,
three in the draft
>> a fourth one. Any chance you can put it on the screen for us?
I don't have the ability right
now with this.
>> Would it be helpful for me to put your previous draft up just as a starting point so everybody can see it? Sure, that'd be great. Jabil, could you just email it to me real quick and I'll share it?
I don't know. I think if I go,
I'm on an email,
I'm on your email to get here and so if I back out, last time I backed out to send that email out to everybody, it tripped me out of Zoom and I had to come back in.
Jim, can you forward your copy to Eric by email right now?
I'm not able to do that. No. Okay.
>> Alright. Well, Jim, why don't you tell us We what it can write it down and
and just
make the motion. We'll just make the motion.
Move it up. Let
>> me put up what we had and then Jim can tell us the changes to it. Sure.
Everybody see that?
Yep. Okay.
So I think,
well Jim, walk us through it. I think the first paragraph you'll probably stays the same.
>> Move that the Planning Zoning Commission recommend that the boarder selected to move forward with the acquisition
of the 162
acres of land owned by Donnell family for a judge on Shawnee Mill Road.
Boundary survey filed at map eighty eight forty one of the land records.
More particularly, PCC recommends the following one.
Town move forward with an application for matching funds through the state state of Connecticut's open space and watershed protection program.
Two, all funds in the town's open space fund as of this date, eightthirty onetwenty two, be made available as the town's match.
Such funds shall be made available for acquisition and ancillary expenses. The latter shall include, but not limited to, the cost of a review appraisal, construction of parking area, gate, and signage.
Number three, the Board of Selectmen,
this is another recommendation. Board of Selectmen authorize the town administrator
to enter negotiations
with the property owner and execute a purchase and sale agreement prepared by the town attorney with the requisite contingencies.
And I added a fourth that
the Planning and Zoning Commission
authorized Jed to submit a letter of support for the actual grant application itself on behalf of the Commission.
>> Oh, it's number four again, Jed. Say that one again. That
>> the commission authorized
its chairman
to prepare
a letter of support for the grant application
on behalf of the commission.
Should you
>> offer That's just, it's a component of the application.
And
a number of letters of support will be submitted as part of the application, one of them being the planning and zoning commissions.
>> Okay. Okay. So the commission authorizes Jed to offer
a letter of support for the application?
>> Yes.
To to prepare a letter of support.
To accompany the application.
>> So Jim's
got the motion
and he's right in the minute, I know he will get the motion correctly
into the minutes from tonight.
Any so
I
make a motion
to
approve what Jim just led us through.
Which is essentially the
three points we're looking at plus the fourth that I'll prepare a letter of support.
Correct, I'll second that. Okay, thank you Scott. Any
discussion by any of the commission members?
Hearing none,
I'll call for a vote. Anne?
Aye.
>> Scott?
Steve?
Aye.
Leigh Ann?
And I vote
aye as well. The motion passes five-zero-zero.
Anything else you were looking for
tonight on that, Hank or Eric?
>> No. Not that I can think of, not on my end.
>> Okay, well,
on behalf of the Commission, I appreciate the effort that both of you do, especially you, Hank,
have put into this. I think it's
a good thing. It allows us to do something that, know, back in 2015,
we said we wanted to do. So it's about time. I don't know that
we'll be successful, but we're certainly giving it
a good effort to try and pull it off. So
thank you
>> very much. Well, thank you to the Commission for again taking the time on short notice to have a special meeting
and also to Jim and Eric for all of their efforts
on a short notice to pull some of this work together.
>> Okay, I'm going to move on to item four, public speak. I don't think anybody
want to speak from the public perspective?
It's better to burn out than to fade away.
>> The next regularly scheduled meeting is coming up on September
21.
And I will make a motion that we adjourn.
Second.
>> It's just as easy to do a roll call vote on that. So, Anne?
Aye.
>> Scott? Aye.
Steve? Aye. Leanne?
Aye. And I vote aye as well. Motion to adjourn passes five zero zero.
Thank you everybody. Yeah, go ahead Leanne.
>> Is the next meeting on Monday the nineteenth or
Wednesday the twenty first? Oh,
>> nineteenth.
Nineteenth, my my my. Nineteenth. Okay. Yep. Keep on calling it a Wednesday.
Thank
you, Leanne.